Corey Greeneltch

703.785.8550 corey@blanksky.com www.blanksky.com

An award-winning, hands-on Design Director with a track record of success in planning and executing the design of elegant and easy to use digital experiences that produce positive impact on brand, engagement, and return on investment. Excels in leading, recruiting, developing, and mentoring cross-functional teams and setting high standards for design, user experience and innovation.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Creative Team Leadership • Brand/UI Evolution • Digital/Social Media • System Design
User Research • UX design • Team Building/Leadership • Training & Development
Product Development Process • Product Innovation • Responsive Design • Brand Design
Product Design • Experience Design • Agile • Discovery Workshops • Stakeholder Presentation

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Collaborated with the DoD and VA to design and develop eBenefits, a website for veterans benefits that now has over 5 million users.

Worked closely with the in-house design team and external contractors to **relaunch USATODAY.com** in 2012.

In 2013, led the effort to create an enterprise design system for the 100+ local properties, maintaining previous functionality and establishing brand standards for Gannett digital properties.

Established Gannett's first in-house IA team, standardized user testing practices across the company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Director of Product Design Gannett/USA TODAY NETWORK

2012-present

Built and led a team of 20 designers and architects responsible for the enterprise UX of Gannett's universal framework across 120+ national and local properties. Led creation of wireframes, prototypes, mockups and user testing. Worked closely with executive stakeholders, communicating project goals and status.

- Created efficient project processes, enabling better collaboration between architects, designers and developers
- Responsible for evolution of USA TODAY and local media brands and experiences across apps and web
- Managed, mentored and recruited designers & architects
- Responsible for new product design featuring innovative new revenue streams

Art Director
USA TODAY

Managed a team of designers responsible for the overall UX of the USATODAY.com website as well as interactive editorial projects.

- Led design for 2012 Elections experience on USA TODAY.com website and native apps.
- Worked closely with clients to create unique content-focused advertising opportunities.
- Creative direction for award-winning interactives.

Art Director 2008-2010

Ironworks

Responsible for user experience design, interaction design and development, presentation design, user research, usability testing and social media strategy. Worked with clients such as The Department of Veterans Affairs, The Nature Conservancy, MeadWestvaco, The United States Navy, and Campbell's. Major initiatives include designing and developing eBenefits brand and user experience for the Dept of Veterans Affairs. Worked with PBS to design the user experience for PBS Teachers Connect, an online education community. Redesigned Discovery's National Body Challenge website.

Publications Chair 2009-2010

Art Directors Club of Washington DC

Responsibilities include editorial management of FullBleed, the club's online magazine. Determining strategy, working with volunteers, brainstorming article topics, finding authors, publishing, designing and developing article layouts.

Asst Art Director 2003-2008

Vertex Solutions

Produced award-winning campaigns in the government learning space. Managed projects and team members on campaigns, websites, interactive applications and online courseware for clients such as MedImmune, TSA, USDA, DHS, Smithsonian, Air Force, and many others.

Multimedia Specialist 1998-2003

Advanced Presentations

Led design for web, multimedia and print collateral, including Flash, Director, and web projects. Contributed conceptual directions for materials and internal projects. Managed Jr. Designers, projects and clients.

EDUCATION

BA, Studio Art, University of Mary Washington

1994-1998

2010-2012